{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of France?",
            "options": [
                "London",
                "Paris",
                "New York",
                "Tokyo"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the 23rd president of the US ?",
            "options": [
                "George Washington",
                "Abraham Lincoln",
                "Benjamin Harrison",
                "Barak Obama"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How many months in a year have 28 days?",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "1",
                "1,but not every year, but once every 4 year",
                "3"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How many men does it take to dig half a hole?",
            "options": [
                "10",
                "2",
                "1",
                "0,you can't dig half a hole"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How many zeroes are there in 1 million?",
            "options": [
                "6",
                "4",
                "3",
                "5"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one among the following lays eggs and does not produce young ones directly?",
            "options": [
                "Whale",
                "Porcupine",
                "Echidna",
                "Kangaroo"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "O multiplied by any number gives the result as ________?",
            "options": [
                "1",
                "The Same Number",
                "Undefined",
                "0"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the smallest bird?",
            "options": [
                "Hummingbird",
                "Parrot",
                "House sparrow",
                "Pigeon"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What year was NASA founded?",
            "options": [
                "1948",
                "1960",
                "1958",
                "2009"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first man on moon?",
            "options": [
                "Lance Armstrong",
                "My mom",
                "Neil Armstrong",
                "George Washington"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which among the following produces honey?",
            "options": [
                "Flying ant",
                "Hornet",
                "Bee",
                "Wasp"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which number should come next in the series? 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, ___",
            "options": [
                "10",
                "11",
                "13",
                "21"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        }
    ]
}